jewelry.com 2017-09-30

# Privacy Policy

## Jewelry.com will occasionally update its privacy statement to reflect company and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we are protecting your information. If you have questions or concerns about our policy, you should first contact us. Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy is designed to inform you of what information Jewelry.com collects, why we collect such information and how we use the information we collect.

### Collection And Use Of Information:

In general, you can browse our Web Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. Personally identifiable information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name; home, billing or other physical address; an email address; phone number or other contact information. When you submit your personally identifiable information to us, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as set forth in this privacy policy.

As a policy, Jewelry.com does not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to third-parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

Please note that we have the ability to retain any data that you provide on this website, even if you do not complete your registration or transaction by clicking “Register,” “Submit,” or any similar Action Link. Your contact information (for example, your email address) may be used to contact you a single time with a special offer or to provide sales assistance. By using this website you are agreeing to these terms.

### Communications:

If you provide Jewelry.com with personally identifiable information, this information may be used to communicate to you information regarding Jewelry.com and its services. For example, we may communicate to you information regarding promotions, surveys, contests, sweepstakes or product or service updates. Your personally identifiable information may also be used to improve and customize our Web Site’s content, layout and services. These uses improve and customize our interactions with you to better meet your needs.

If you do not want to receive communications from Jewelry.com you may elect to opt-out of receiving such communications; please see the “Choice/Opt-Out” section below for more information.

### Internal Use:

We may compare and review your personally identifiable information for errors, omissions and accuracy. We may also use your personally identifiable information internally to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, Web Site content and product offerings. Your personally identifiable information may also be used internally to conduct internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, behavior and generally to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Web Site and our marketing programs.

### Compliance With Law And Fraud Protection:

We may collect and disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may collect and possibly share personally identifiable information and any other information available to us in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise required by law. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

### Service Providers:

We may share your personally identifiable information with authorized third party partners, agents and contractors. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. Examples of other third parties that we may share your personal information with include: web hosting companies, fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fulfill product orders), jewelers, assemblers, data analysis firms, affiliates, third party consulting or marketing firms and e-mail service providers. These third parties only receive personally identifiable information if such information is needed to perform their function(s), and they are not authorized to use any personally identifiable information for any other purpose(s) other than the purpose(s) set forth by Jewelry.com. We only provide third-parties with the minimum amount of personally identifiable information necessary to complete the requested service, product or transaction.

### Special Events:

If you choose to participate in a special event (for example, a promotion, contest or sweepstake), Jewelry.com may share your personally identifiable information with those organizations participating in the applicable event. Typically, these third parties do not use your information for any other purpose other than to manage the event. In some cases these third-party partners may send you promotional materials regarding their products and services. In these cases, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out, and not have your personally identifiable information shared with that third-party partner.

If at any time you choose to enter a Jewelry.com feedback contest and allow us to post your feedback on our Web Site, we will remove your feedback from our Web Site at any time if you send your request via e-mail to 

### IP Address:

When you visit our Web Site, Jewelry.com collects your IP address to, among other things, help diagnose problems with its server, administer and tune the operation of its Web Site, analyze trends, track traffic patterns, gather demographic information for aggregate use, and track the date and duration of each session within our Web Site. Your IP address may also be used in combination with your personally identifiable information for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

### Data Collection Devices, Such As Cookies And Web Beacons:

In some instances, Jewelry.com may collect non-personal data through cookies, web logs, web beacons (also know as pixel gifs or action tags) and other monitoring technologies. Where authorized by us, third parties may use cookies, Jewelry.com’s web log files, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile aggregate statistics on Jewelry.com’s behalf. The non-personal information that we collect is used to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Web Site and marketing programs. We may share or transfer non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies on certain pages of our Web Site to, among other things, analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, deliver you a more customized shopping experience, track visits from our affiliates and partners and allow the use of our Save and Recently Viewed lists. Jewelry.com does not use cookies to store or collect any personally identifiable information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits; although, by declining the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the Web Site. Jewelry.com Web pages may also contain electronic images know as Web beacons. These Web beacons allow Jewelry.com to count users who have visited certain Web pages or to deliver co-branded services. Jewelry.com may also include Web beacons in its email messages in order to determine whether the message has been opened or acted upon.

Additionally, Jewelry.com may use third-party advertising or content delivery companies to serve ads or images on our Web Site or on other web sites on the World Wide Web. These companies may use web beacons to place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the third party to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compiles anonymous information. Information collected through these third-party advertising companies is anonymous.

### Children Under 13:

Jewelry.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems. Please visit the FTC’s website at [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/) for tips on protecting children’s privacy online.

### Links:

Our Web Site may provide links to other third-party Web Sites that are outside our control and not covered by this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) Web Sites.

### Security:

Jewelry.com is committed to the protection of the personally identifiable information that you share with us. We utilize a combination of security technologies, procedures and organizational measures to help protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers with limited access. Additionally, when we transfer sensitive personal information (for example, credit card information) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.

### Updating Your Information:

If the personally identifiable information Jewelry.com has gathered from you changes or you would like to revise such information, we will gladly correct or update any personal data you have previously provided to us. To request a change or update to your personal information, please send an e-mail to 

### Choice/Opt-out:

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. To opt-out of receiving communications from Jewelry.com: 

  1. (recommended) Select the “unsubscribe” link from within any Jewelry.com email correspondence; or
  2. Select “unsubscribe” on our Edit Registration page when logged in; or
  3. make your request by contacting us at 

Should you have any difficulty unsubscribing, have any questions, or need assistance, please contact us at, or at 1-800-243-0459, or at 1385 Broadway, 12th Floor, New York, NY 10018.

### Your Consent To Jewelry.com’s Privacy Policy:

By using this Web Site, you agree to Jewelry.com’s privacy policy. This is our entire and exclusive privacy policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may occasionally update this privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are protecting your information. Your continued use of this Web Site constitutes your consent to this privacy policy and any updates.

### Questions, Comments, Contact:

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact the Jewelry.com customer service department at. You may also send us your comments about the Jewelry.com Web Site or the shopping experience in general, as we always appreciate feedback.

We can be reached by phone at 1-800-243-0459 from 9am-5pm (Eastern Time), or by mail at 1385 Broadway, 12th Floor, New York, NY 10018
